(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-24T23:14:29.070795",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Wait, this is good.
I did it!
I infiltrated this place!
Success!
大作戦だ！
It's a grand mission!
あ、みんなに見られた！
Ah, everyone saw me!
I can't believe you guys were watching me this whole time... No!
To be honest, I did feel... I did feel eyes on me,
but I knew you guys were watching. It's okay.
Anyways, it's not the time to be talking about that because...
...today is a special day for me! For me!
Today is... do you know what day it is?
Say it, say it! Say it, say it! Say it!
Yeah, today is my birthday!
Happy birthday Zeta, Happy birthday Zeta...
...Selamat ulang tahun...
...Happy birthday to you...
Gitu kan sih lagunya? I don't know.
Is that how the song goes? I don't know.
Oh, what? You're saying something?
Huh? No...
Skill... skill... skill issue?
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bulls... Okay, I can't say that word...
Bulls... You're lying, you're lying!
That can't be true! I've been working hard.
I've got the stamina, and obviously the intelligence...
IQ... IQ nihyakku!
IQ... IQ 200!
And strength, you know? Got the power as well.
So anyways, don't you worry because I've got the perfect thing for today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Have you ever heard of...
...of... of a secret agent school?
Yeah, so... back in my days, I've been through hell and back.
So, I invited some transfer students here so we can prove that I'm the best secret agent, okay?
So we're going to do some tests together to see...
...how tough it is to become a professional secret agent like me! Like me, like me!
Anyways, it reminds me of my... um... old Gakko-ism, you know?
Anyways, it reminds me of my... um... old school days, you know?
But, to be honest... to be honest, to be honest...
...I don't know what we'll be doing yet, but...
Wait, oh crap! Okay, it's almost time for the first test.
うわー！そいつのテストが…
Whoa! That test...
そろそろ…
...is starting soon...
早く行かないと！
I have to go quickly!
Bye!
これは…！
What is this...?!
なんかさ、あれ？
Wait, what's that?
ゾンビ？
A zombie?
どりゃー！
Hiyah!
あれ？なんか…
Wait, what's with him?
あれ？なんかみこちのカマキリの威嚇ポーズにビビってる？
Wait, is he scared of Mikochi's praying mantis threat pose?
あ、ビビってる？ビビってる！
Ah, is he scared? He's totally scared!
べろべろべろ〜！あれ？
Bero bero bero~! Huh?
これ、みこちゃん分かりました。こいつ、雑魚ゾンビです。
I've got it. This guy is a total scrub zombie.
ざ〜こ、ざ〜こ！
Loser, loser!
あ、泣いちゃった！
Ah, he's crying!
こいつ、ドMかもしれない！ドMゾンビ！もっと言え、もっと言え。
He might be a total masochist! A masochist zombie! Say more, say more!
ポンコツ〜！
You piece of junk!
あ、効いてる効いてる。もしかして…あ、じゃあみこちゃんも言って。
Oh, it's working. No way... Ah, you go too, Mikochi.
ざぁ〜こ。
Loser.
効いてる、効いてる！珍しい！
It's working! How unusual!
ちょっと弱々ゾンビさんなんじゃない？全然怖くないんですけど。余裕かも！
Maybe he's just a really weak zombie? I'm not scared of him at all. This is a breeze!
う〜、う〜。
Uuu~, uuu~.
みんな！
Everyone!
あ、ゼタ！お誕生日おめでとう！
Ah, Zeta! Happy birthday!
おめでとう！何これ？このゾンビ。
Thanks! What's with this zombie?
あれは弱々ゾンビ。弱々ゾンビがいるの。
That's a super weak zombie. We have a weak zombie here.
エージェントスクールの最初のテストにお招きしたけど、ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
I invited you all to the Agent School's first test, but I wonder if the zombie is also a freshman?
新入生？新入生なの？大丈夫なの？
A freshman? Is he a freshman? Is that okay?
そうんだ。でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。ゼタは色んな言葉話せるよね？ゾンビ語も喋れるんじゃないの？
I see. But we can't communicate with zombies. Zeta, you can speak many languages, right? Can't you speak zombie-ese too?
え、ちょっと待って…喋って、喋って。喋って？オッケー、オッケー。
Eh, wait a minute... Speak it, speak it! Speak it? Okay, okay.
うー、行け！うわあああああ！
Urgh, here I go! Uwaaaah!
あれ？なんか会話してる？い、いや、いや、いや…よし、できた。
Wait, are they having a conversation? N-No, no, no... Alright, I did it.
できたの？！できた。
You did?! I did.
おい、ゾンビ！何してるの！怖がらせろって言ったでしょ！
Hey, zombie! What are you doing?! I told you to be scary, right?!
本当に何やってたのよ！
What have you been doing?!
Apologies. I probably sent over the weak zombies. Sorry about that.
Anyways, I called you guys here for a surprise test to see if you guys are fit to be a secret agent.
よくわかんないけど受ける！よくわかんないけど受けてみるか。
I don't really get it, but I'll do it! Let's give it a try.
Okay, okay. Calm down everyone. In this test, you will need to guess what is inside the box!
This requires your investigative skills. For round 1, you can feel the object for 30 seconds only. Have fun!
Can't wait to see your reactions.
完全に理解したから。本当に？
I completely understand now. Really?
じゃあ、AZKi先輩からかな？私？任せてくださいよ！
Shall we start with AZKi-senpai? Me? Leave it to me!
頑張って！これってみんなで協力してだよね？
Good luck! We're doing this by cooperating, right?
伝えることに集中したいと思います。いいよ！
I'll focus on describing what it feels like. Sounds good!
Three, two, one, start!
えっ？これ…えっ？
Eh? What is this?
えっと、コードのような…コード？ちぎれたコードのようなものではない？
Let's see, it feels like a cord... A cord? No, wait, it's not like a broken cord?
えっ、ちょっと待って！うわああ！何これ？！
Wait a minute! Whoa! What is this?!
なんか、じたばたしてます、じたばた。
It's thrashing around! It's squirming!
じたばた、なんか動いてる！動いてる？！
It's squirming, it's moving! It's moving?!
え、なんか動いているけど…！
Wait, it's definitely moving...!
Time's up!
何だ？何だ？何それ？
What is it? What is it? What is that?
なんか、足がバタバタしてる。
Its legs are flailing about.
バタバタ？！やばい！
Leg flailing?! That's bad!
じゃあ、ミオちゃん！スタート！
Now, Mio-chan! Start!
お、お、お…
Oh, oh, oh...
怖い、怖い！何、何、何？
Scary, scary! What is it?
は、なんか、あっ！あ！
Huh, wait, ah! Ah!
でも分かったかも、これ私。
But I might know what this is.
あ、なるほど。はいはいはい！あ、元気ですね！
Oh, I see. Okay, okay! Ah, it's very energetic!
元気？！元気です？！完全に生きてます。
Energetic?! It's energetic?! It's definitely alive.
Time's up!
あ、元気だったな、すごい元気。絶対に生きてるんだ。ちょっと待って。
Ah, it was so energetic, really lively. It's definitely alive. Wait a minute.
ゴッドハンド、ゴッドハンドで…
God Hand... God Hand...
ゴッドハンド、よろしくお願いいたします。
Please do your best with your God Hand.
3、2、1、ゴー！
Three, two, one, go!
主治医、絶対嫌だ！
I'd hate to have her as my doctor!
きゃー！
Kyaa!
いや！ちょっと待って！
No! Wait!
待った！待った待った待った！
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
なんかに触れた模様。
It seems I touched something.
きゃー！
Kyaa!
やめろ！
Stop that!
ガチですか？
Are you serious?
ガチなやつ。ガチなやつだ。
She is serious. That's for real.
いやだ！もうやだ！
No! No, no!
きゃー！いやだ！
Kyaaa! No!
真剣な表情。
She has a very serious expression.
わ、わかった？
Did you get it?
全然分かんない。
I have no idea at all.
え？全然終わりじゃない？
What? It's not over yet!
終わりだよ！ / え、終わりだよ！
It is over! / Yeah, it's over.
え？ゴッドハンド？
What? Is this the God Hand?
なんかぶるるるってなって。 / メッチャキモい！
It felt like it was vibrating wildly. / That's so gross!
じゃあ次はゼータ！
Okay, next up is Zeta!
次はゼータ、ゼータの番！いけー！
Next is Zeta! Zeta's turn! Go!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
[Title: Vestia Zeta's Challenge]
いきますよー！
Here we go!
3、2、1、スタート！
Three, two, one, start!
飛ぶぞ、あいつ。
Is she going to jump?
うわ、何これ何これ？！
Eww, what is this?!
ええー！これ生きてるやん！
Wait, is this thing alive?!
いや、多分生きてないような気がするけど…
I don't think it's alive, though.
ええー？ええー？口？え、何これ？
What is this? Is it a mouth? What?!
なんかちゃんと触っています。
She is touching it properly.
形を確認しているのでしょうか。大丈夫かな？
Is she trying to identify its shape? Is she okay?
え？飛んでる？これ飛んでる？
Is it flying? Is it flying?
なんか飛びそうではあるよね。
It looks like it could jump, though.
飛びそうだよね、これ。
Right? It seems like it'll jump.
飛びそう？ / うわー！生きてる！
It'll jump? / Oh, it's alive!
生きているのか、なんなのか。
Is it alive or what?
いや、これちょっと…
Wow, this is...
え、でもこれみんなでね。
Wait, we have to guess it together.
力を合わせてね。 / そうだね、そうだね。力を合わせて、誰が答える？
Yes, let's pool our strength. / Who is going to answer?
なんかプロペラみたいなのがついてたのかなって思ったんだけど。
I thought it had some kind of propeller on it.
マジでみこの手に触れたのがぶるるるってなったから。
But when it touched my hand, it went crazy!
アヒルとかの足がこうなんか…
Maybe it's like a duck whose feet...
バタバタバタバタってなってるのか、バタバタバタバタみたいな。
...flutter rapidly when wound up?
みお先輩は？
What about Mio-senpai?
これはズバリ、カエルのおもちゃです！
To put it simply, it's a frog toy!
ぴょこぴょこ。 / ぴょこぴょこしてたってこと？
It goes hop, hop. / So it was hopping?
ゼータちゃん、みんなのこの回答まとめよう。
Zeta, summarize all our answers.
ええー！ / お願いします、まとめてください。
What?! / Please, summarize it for us.
みお先輩の答えで。
Let's go with Mio-senpai's answer.
自信満々だったもんね。 / まあ確かに自信満々だった。これで間違ってたらうちのド先輩。
She was so confident, after all. / If she's wrong, she'll be demoted.
カエルのおもちゃかな。
Maybe a frog toy?
みんなのあれだからね。 / じゃあカエルのおもちゃで！
Well, it's based on everyone's input. / Let's go with frog toy!
お、よくできました！
You did very well!
合ってる！カエルのおもちゃだ！すごーい！
We got it right! It really is a frog toy!
すごい、みおちゃん！
Mio-chan, that's amazing!
何がポイントだったんですか？
What made you think so?
触った感じがピタピタしてて。
The texture felt sticky and damp.
あ、ピタピタもあれか。
Ah, that sticky rubbery texture.
で、なんかね、ぴょんぴょんぴょんってしてたから。
And it felt like it was hopping.
そうそうそう！ / あ、これカエルのおもちゃっぽいなって思った。
Yes, exactly! / So I thought it must be a frog toy.
すごい！素晴らしい！
Amazing! Wonderful!
じゃあ次の問題、お願いします！
Now, on to the next question, please!
じゃあうちがいってみますか。 / ゴッドハンドミオ。
Should I go next? / God Hand Mio!
いきますか。ゴッドハンドミオ、ゴッドハンドミオ。
God Hand Mio, let's go!
大神ミオの挑戦
[Title: Ookami Mio's Challenge]
がんばれ！ / スタート！
Do your best! / Start!
何それ？ / 怖い怖い、ホラー！
What is that?! / It's so scary! It's like a horror game!
ミオちゃんが怖がっている。
Mio-chan is terrified.
え？何が？
Wait, what is it?
嘘でしょ、何これ？
No way! What is this?!
怖！何なんだよこれ、気持ち悪い！
Creepy! What on earth is this? It's disgusting!
え？ええ？気持ち悪い？ / 気持ち悪い？
Disgusting? / Disgusting?
何これ！何これ！
What is this?! What is this?!
怖い怖い怖い！
It's so scary!
なんか、大袈裟じゃない？その反応。
Wait, isn't she overreacting a bit?
そういうこと？ / え？何？
Is that what's going on? / What is it?!
いや！いやーーー！
No! Nooo!
大袈裟にやってるんじゃないの？ / なんか嫌だ。ちょっと行ってみて行ってみて、これちょっと。
You were just acting, right? / I hated that. Try it yourself!
あずき行け。 / あずき先輩頑張れ！
AZKi, go ahead. / AZKi-senpai, do your best!
AZKiの挑戦
[Title: AZKi's Challenge]
はは、優しそうだね。 / え、何これ？
It feels kind of soft. / Really?
え？何？ / ええ？
Wait, what? / What is it?
いや、その反応になるって。
See? I told you you'd react like that.
もしゃもしゃしてます。
It feels fluffy and hairy.
もしゃもしゃ？ / ヒントは？
Fluffy? / Any hints?
もしゃもしゃ。もしゃもしゃ。
Fluffy, fluffy...
なんかベタベタしてた。 / ベタベタ？え、キモい。何それ？
And it's sticky. / Sticky? Gross, what is it?
キモい。 / でもこれ、多分。これは何かのパーツ。
It's gross. / But I think this is... It might be a part of something.
タッチって言われたらむずいけど。
It's hard to describe the texture.
え、なんかちょっと心にダメージ受けるよね、これ。 / ダメージ受けた。
This really deals some emotional damage. / I felt that damage.
次行くか！
Let's move on!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
[Title: Vestia Zeta's Challenge]
スタート！
Start!
ああ！ああ！
Ah! Ah!
初手、初手驚くよね。
You get surprised on the first touch, right?
そう、最初は驚くよね、これ。
Yeah, you get surprised at first with this.
ええー？
Eeeh?
あーーー！
Ahhhh!
でも、柔らかい。柔らかい。
But it's soft. Soft.
柔らかい？
Soft?
優しい。
Gentle.
優しい！？
Gentle!?
優しい、柔らかい。
Gentle and soft.
これに関してはちょっとね、ゼータの感覚が狂ってるかも知れない。
Regarding this, Zeta's senses might be a bit messed up.
えええー？
Eeeh?
何何何？避けて！怖いんだけど！
What what what? Move away! It's scary!
え？いいのか？ここで。
Wait, is this okay? Here...
いいのか？
Is it okay?
いいのか？ここで。うん。
Is this okay here? Yeah.
じゃあ、みこ先輩がんばってね。
Then, Miko-senpai, do your best!
待って、待って。
Wait, wait.
おっと、ゴッドハンド...
Oops, the God Hand...
出た！出た！ゴッドハンド！
He's out! He's out! God Hand!
いや、これはゴッドリアクションですよ。
No, this is a God Reaction.
ゴッドリアクション来るか？
Is the God Reaction coming?
さくらみこの挑戦
[Title: Sakura Miko's Challenge]
スタート！
Start!
うわーーー！！！
Ahhhh!!!
来た！ゴッドリアクション！
It's here! God Reaction!
ゴッドリアクションしてる。
She's doing a God Reaction.
いやーーー！！！
Noooo!!!
うわーーー！！！
Ahhhh!!!
待って待って待って。
Wait, wait, wait.
ためらっています。
She is hesitating.
手を入れることをためらっているが...
She is hesitating to put her hand in, but...
ためらうよね、これ。一回、一回聞いたもん。
You'd hesitate with this, since she heard that once.
うわーーー！！！
Ahhhh!!!
待って、なんか...
Wait, something...
息を吸うじゃないか。
She is taking breaths.
息を吸う...
Taking breaths...
待って、何これ？
Wait, what is this?
何これ、ってなるよな。
You'd wonder what this is.
食べ物？いや、そんなことはない。
Food? No, that can't be.
何だろうね。
What could it be?
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
なんか、濡れてる...
Something's wet...
ちょっとやばいことが起きてるじゃないか。
Isn't something crazy happening?
え？やばいこと？
Eh? Something crazy?
箱の中で。
Inside the box.
事件が起きている！
A crime is happening!
マスクをしてたと思うねん。だからうちは、ピエロのマスクなんじゃないかと思いました。
I think it was wearing a mask, so I thought maybe it's a clown mask.
ええと、白い、白塗りの、女性の、顔？
Um, a white, white-painted, woman's face?
怖えよ！
That's scary!
マスク？マスクか。マスク！
A mask? Is it a mask? Mask!
そ、その答え、怖えよ！
Th-That answer is scary!
おそらく、うーんと、YAGOOのカツラ。
Probably, hmm, YAGOO's wig.
えええー？
Eeeh?
絶対カツラだったと思うんだよ、あれ。
I really think that was a wig.
ロングヘアーYAGOO？いや、ロングヘアーYAGOO？
Long-haired YAGOO? Wait, long-haired YAGOO?
そう、可能性...
Yeah, the possibility...
可能性高い。
High possibility.
名探偵みこ先輩に信じようかな。
Should I believe Detective Miko-senpai?
お、お？
Oh, oh?
答えは...
The answer is...
ロングヘアーYAGOO！
Long-haired YAGOO!
YAGOO！
YAGOO!
あちゃー、残念だね。
Ah, too bad.
不正解です！
Incorrect!
なんか怖いんだけど。
Something is scary, though.
幽霊のマスク
Ghost Mask
当たってた！
I was right!
うわーーー！！！
Ahhhh!!!
当たってる！当たってるよ！当たってる！
I was right! I was right! I was right!
当たってるの、怖い！
Being right is scary!
次の問題、お願いします。
Next question, please.
お願いします！
Please!
じゃあ、みこちゃんから行って。
Then, Miko-chan, you go first.
ゴッドハンドみこちゃんが行ってみました。
God Hand Miko-chan went first.
名探偵。
Detective.
名探偵決めてね、ここで。
Detective, decide here.
名探偵、頼むよ。
Detective, we're relying on you.
さくらみこの挑戦
[Title: Sakura Miko's Challenge]
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go go go!
うわーーー！！！
Ahhhh!!!
待って、さっきより...
Wait, compared to earlier...
待って、濡れてる！
Wait, it's wet!
ちょっと今日一の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
Wait, we got the loudest scream of the day, is she okay?
うわー！
Ahhh!
え？え？
Eh? Eh?
いやーーー！！！
Noooo!!!
実況してよ！
Give us commentary!
実況実況！
Commentary, commentary!
なんかチクチクしてて...
It's like, prickly...
チクチク？
Prickly?
痛いってこと？
Does it mean it hurts?
なんか、ぬるぬるっていうか、濡れてて！
Like, slimy, or rather, it's wet!
濡れてる！？
Wet!?
濡れてる！
Wet!
全部に...
On everything...
あの、トゲトゲがあります！
there are, like, prickles!
全部にトゲトゲがある？
Everything has prickles?
で、いっぱいいる！
And there are lots of them!
いっぱいいる？
Lots of them?
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
トゲトゲした生き物？
Prickly creatures?
待って、いっぱいいるって何？
Wait, what do you mean by lots of them?
はあ...
(sighs)
え？何何何？
Eh? What what what?
いっぱいいる...
There are lots of them...
どうする？
What should we do?
あずき先輩が行くほうがいいかな。
Maybe AZKi-senpai should go?
冷静な判断、できるのか？
Can she make a calm judgment?
AZKiの挑戦
[Title: AZKi's Challenge]
あずき先輩、ゴー！
AZKi-senpai, go!
へ？何？
Heh? What?
お？え？
Oh? Eh?
なんか濡れてる。
Something is wet.
濡れてる！？
Wet!?
やっぱ濡れてるんだ。
Ah, it really is wet.
え、なんか、湿って...
Eh, like, damp...
湿っています。
It is damp.
湿ってる？
Damp?
湿度高めなんだ、これ。
The humidity is high for this.
どういうこと？
What does that mean?
え、何この...
Eh, what is this...
うん、トゲトゲした、あの、球体のような。
Yeah, prickly, um, like a sphere...
球体？
Sphere?
球体と、その下にもトゲトゲしたものが...
A sphere, and below it there are also prickly things...
トゲトゲがいっぱいあるんだ。
So there are lots of prickles.
まあ、痛くはないけど...
Well, it doesn't hurt, but...
痛くはないの？
It doesn't hurt?
え、これ何だ？
Eh, what is this?
何なんだろう。
What could it be?
何なのかがわからなくなってきた。
I've stopped understanding what it is...
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
めっちゃムズいんだ、じゃあ。
Then it's super hard!
何だこれー！
What is this!
めっちゃ湿ってる！
It's super damp!
みおちゃんですかね、次。
Mio-chan is next, right?
最後、ゼータに決めてもらおう。
At the end, let's have Zeta decide.
さあさあさあ。
Come on, come on, come on.
なんか嫌だな、その感想聞いた状態でやる、触るのちょっと嫌だかも。
I don't like this, touching it after hearing those impressions makes me a bit reluctant.
大神ミオの挑戦
[Title: Ookami Mio's Challenge]
ゴー！
Go!
嫌だな、濡れてるって前情報で嫌だ。
I hate this, knowing it's wet beforehand makes me hate it.
濡れてる...
Wet...
あ、やっぱり...
Ah, as I thought...
濡れてるな。
It's wet, indeed.
濡れてる？
Wet?
おお、濡れてる。
Oh, it's wet.
ええー？
Eeeh?
けど...
But...
濡れてるけど...
It's wet, but...
なんか固くて...
it's somewhat hard...
確かにたくさんいる。
and indeed there are lots of them.
たくさんいる？
Lots of them?
たくさんいるぞ。
There are lots of them!
一体何なんだろう？
What on earth is it?
うん。これは...
Yeah. This is...
何だ？
What is it?
え、これでもさ、あんまり見かけないやつの気がする。
Eh, but with this, I feel like it's something we don't see very often.
見かけない？
Don't see?
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
お互いに？
Is it hard for everyone?
これ、むずいんじゃない？
Isn't this hard?
え、むずい？
Eh, is it hard?
ゼータ、行こう！
Zeta, let's go!
ゼータ！
Zeta!
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
[Title: Vestia Zeta's Challenge]
スタート！
Start!
おお？
Oh?
ああ！
Ah!
あ、オッケー、オッケー。
Ah, okay, okay.
あ、オッケー？
Oh, okay?
早い！
That was fast!
もしかしてこれさ…
Could this be...
オッケー、わかる。
Okay, I get it.
我々はあんまり馴染みないけど、
We might not be familiar with it,
ゼータは馴染みある…
but Zeta is familiar with it...
馴染みあるの？
Is she familiar with it?
もしかしたら。
Maybe.
これ、いっぱい触ったことあるかも。
I might have touched this a lot.
ええ？馴染み深い？
Eh? It's familiar?
馴染み深いんだよ、きっと。インドネシア。
It must be familiar. To Indonesia.
何だろう？
What is it?
オッケー。
Okay.
我々にしたら、ちょっと難しいかも。
For us, it might be a bit difficult.
イェーイ！
Yay!
おそらく、これは…
Probably, this is...
ウニの仲間。
a relative of the sea urchin.
ウニ？
Sea urchin?
アズキの答えは？
Azuki, what's your answer?
コケ！
Moss!
なんかこう、ちょっとずついっぱいなんか生えている感じ。
Like something that grows a little bit in large numbers.
でも、確かに湿ってたしね。
But it was indeed damp.
うちの答えは、ライチ！
My answer is lychee!
ライチ？
Lychee?
ゼータはね、多分、
For Zeta, probably,
えっと、なんかインドネシアのものと近いかも。
um, it's close to something from Indonesia.
いっぱい、なんか…
There's a lot of, like...
トゲトゲの？
Spiky stuff?
そう、そう。トゲトゲの。
Yes, yes. Spiky.
なんていう食べ物？
What is the food called?
名前は？
The name?
名前はランブータン。ランブータン。
The name is Rambutan. Rambutan.
ランブータン？
Rambutan?
でも、わかんない。これはランブータン…
But I don't know. Is this rambutan...
日本にはいないのかな？
Is it not in Japan?
自信持って！
Have confidence!
そうだよ、ゼータが一番わかってたじゃん。
That's right, Zeta, you understood it the most.
一番自信あったじゃん。
You had the most confidence.
え、じゃあそれでいきましょう。
Eh, then let's go with that.
答えは、せーの！
The answer is, ready, set...
ランブータン！
Rambutan!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding! Correct answer!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ちょっと待って。うちライチとか言ってたけど、全然違うわ。
Wait a second. I said lychee, but it's totally different.
違う！
Different!
ライチの味がするかも。
It might taste like lychee.
ライチに似てる。
It's similar to lychee.
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
美味しいよ、これ。
This is delicious.
初めて見た。
First time seeing it.
甘いの？
Is it sweet?
甘い。甘いんだ。
Sweet. It's sweet.
ちょっと甘酸っぱい。
A bit sweet and sour.
新しい果物に出会いました。
We encountered a new fruit.
There seems to have been correct and incorrect answers.
But...
Zeta! It seems like your investigative skills are not quite up to par yet.
You need to work harder.
Or, in other words...
Skill issue!
スキルイシュー！
見て、スキルイシューのゼータだわ！
Look, it's Zeta with the skill issue!
She's getting mad!
Oh dear! Wow, you can't even solve that!
Everyone else, you did great!
Good luck on the next test!
See y'all!
え、ゼータも頑張ったのにな。
Eh, Zeta worked hard too, though.
ね。
Right?
さっき笑ったの？
Did you laugh earlier?
なんかちょっと舐めてたな。
It was looking down on us a bit.
舐めてたね。
It was looking down on us.
笑ってんじゃねえよ！
Don't laugh at us!
笑ってんじゃねえよ、お前！
Don't laugh at us, you!
そうだ、そうだ！
Yeah, yeah!
一生懸命やったんだろ！
We did our best!
あやまりな！
Apologize!
いじめるな、いじめるな！
Don't bully him!
謝って！
Apologize!
アズキ、アズキ。
Azuki, Azuki.
アズキちゃん、優しい。
Azuki-chan is kind.
もっと床に這いつくばりなさい。
Crawl more on the floor.
アズキさん！？
Azuki-san?!
ドSだ！
She's a sadist!
ありがとうね、みんな来てくれて、本当に。
Thank you everyone for coming, really.
こちらこそ！
Our pleasure!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
あと、今日は集めてくれてありがとうね、本当に。
Also, thank you for gathering today, really.
次のテストの時間だから、行ってくるね。
It's time for the next test, so I'm going.
がんばって！
Good luck!
また会いましょう！
See you again!
ゾンビもっと祝いなさいよ、祝いなさいよ、もっと。
Zombie, celebrate her more, celebrate her more.
ゼータを祝って。
Celebrate Zeta.
Woah, wait. There's like a ring. Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I going to have to do?
No way. Are we going to have to fight? I'm not good at fighting though, but... I mean I can try. Pow, pow, pow, pow!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Long time no see!
This is Amelia Watson, hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good! How are you?
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah, I prepared the second test,
but we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
その名前とあの名セリフを聞けば、誰もが思わず震えるんです！
People tremble when they hear her name and her infamous line!
「小さくてもパワフル、その強さはまさに本物の宝石！レッツ・ロック！」
"Small but mighty, always rock hard. I'm rocking in!"
ご紹介しましょう……古石ビジュー！
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
[古石ビジュー]
[Koseki Bijou]
筋肉を見て、すごい。
Look at her muscles, yeah.
ゼータ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday, Zeta!
今日はあなたのためだけに、カチコチになっちゃうぞ。
Today, I'm rock hard just for you.
ありがとう！光栄です！
Thank you! I'm honored!
私たちが望んだヒーローではないかもしれませんが、
Coming to the ring, she's the hero we didn't ask for,
なぜか信じたくなってしまう存在です！
but somehow still believe in!
最後の希望として現れたのが彼女！ほかのいいヒーローたちが忙しい中、
She's everyone's last hope, because all the good ones were busy!
彼女のセリフは……「滅びを迎え、絶望せよ！はぁっ！」
Her line is: "Meet your end, and... despair! Haiyah!"
[アイリス]
[IRyS]
ゼータ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday, Zeta!
倒してあげる。
I'm taking you down.
さあ皆さん。ダンベルは隠してプライドは覚悟してください！
Ladies and gentlemen, hide your dumbbells and protect your ego!
なぜなら、次に登場するのは魂を狩るだけでなくジムまでぶっ壊しちゃう死神なんです！
Because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls, she rips the gym apart!
彼女の好きなセリフは……「時間だけが、あたしに勝てるベンチプレスよ！」
Her favorite line is: "Only time can out-bench me."
ご紹介しましょう……森カリオペ！
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
[森カリオペ]
[Mori Calliope]
ゼータ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday, Zeta!
来たよ！
I'm here!
よし！みんな揃いましたね？
Good! Everyone has gathered, right?
これはきっとびっくりした人も多いんじゃないでしょうか？
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
そして、みんな気になってますよね？いったいどんなテストなのか！さて、みんな予想はありますか？
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be! Anyone have any guesses?
床叩きじゃないんですよ？
Don't say ground pounding.
あっ、正解です！
Oh, correct!
今回は、この長い棒にBazoくんの重りをつけて挑戦です！
We're holding a physical test using this long stick with these Bazo weights
シークレットエージェントとして通用する体力があるかをテストします！
to determine if you are fit enough to pass off as a secret agent!
すごい、重そう。
Oh my god, okay. That looks heavy.
それでは、体力テストのレベル1にいきましょう！
Okay, okay. For level 1 of the physical test!
30秒の間に、このBazoくんをマットから腰の高さまで、できるだけ多く持ち上げてください！
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
レベル2では、マットがデコボコになります！
For level 2, the mat will be bumpy!
前と同じように、できるだけ多く持ち上げてください！
You'll do the same thing as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
そして最後のレベルでは、デコボコマットの上に立って頭の上にカップを乗せます！
And for the last level, you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head!
カップを落とさないように、Bazoくんを持ち上げてください！
Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
それでは、みんな準備はいいですか？
Well then, are you guys ready?
さあ、レッツゴー！
Let's go!
体力テストを受ける準備はいいですか？
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
ビジュー、まずはあなたからいきましょうか？
Okay, maybe we should have Bijou start first?
任せて。
I got it.
カチコチの筋肉を見せて！
Show us your rock hard muscles!
準備はいいですか？
Okay, are you ready?
スタート！
Start!
1、2、3！
One! Two! Three!
4、5！
Four! Five!
6、7！
Six! Seven!
8、9、10！
Eight! Nine! Ten!
11、12！
Eleven! Twelve!
13、14！
Thirteen! Fourteen!
15、16、17！
Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen!
18、19！
Eighteen! Nineteen!
20、21！
Twenty! Twenty-one!
終了！
Time's up!
[ビジュー レベル1 21]
[Bijou Level 1 21]
さあ、アイリス！
So IRyS!
任せて。
I got this.
見返してやるんだから。
I'm gonna prove some people wrong.
実力を見せて！スタート！
Show your full potential! Start!
1、2、3！
One! Two! Three!
4、5！
Four! Five!
6、7！
Six! Seven!
8、9、10！
Eight! Nine! Ten!
11、12！
Eleven! Twelve!
13、14！
Thirteen! Fourteen!
15、16、17！
Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen!
18、19！
Eighteen! Nineteen!
20、21！
Twenty! Twenty-one!
終了！
Time's up!
[アイリス レベル1 21]
[IRyS Level 1 21]
同点だ！引き分けだね！
Wait, it's a tie, it's a tie!
Like I said, it's more of a speed thing, isn't it?
Show us what you're made of!
Ready, start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen! Oh my god!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen! She's locked in!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two!
Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Oh my god!
Twenty-five! Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine!
Time's up!
Oh, okay, okay!
Anyway, that was Calli's score.
29! Wow!
But like I said, you have to show us what you're made of.
Okay, I got this! You got this, Zeta!
Okay, okay, okay...
You're gonna count for me?
Of course.
Are you ready? Yeah! All right, start!
Start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two!
Twenty-three! Twenty-four!
Twenty-five! Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
Whoa! Nice!
I can't stand up!
You did great! Nice! Look at that score!
30! Wow!
That was easy. She is a secret agent, after all.
That's enough workout for this year!
Yeah!
Okay, now who's ready...
...for Level 2?
I don't know about this one...
Wait, wait a minute! That's not fair!
Those are pebbles! Those are painful!
No, they're not! Those are not pain mats!
That's not fair!
She has an advantage! She's a rock!
Pebbles! You see these?
They're loving it! They're loving it!
Pebbles, you see this?
Oh god, they're loving it. Yeah!
Oh, it hurts so... oh my god, okay, okay!
Okay, start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two!
Twenty-three! Twenty-four!
Twenty-five! Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Thirty-one! Thirty-two!
Thirty-three! Thirty-four!
Was that her full power? Oh my god!
Time's up!
Whoa! Bijou!
Was that her full power?
That's because the rocks were helping her!
They were giving me strength!
Who's next? Who's next? IRyS is next!
Oh no... oh no...
Go on, show the world again...
Show them who you are! Prove you are buff!
Take your time. How does it feel?
Oh god... how does it feel?
Oh god, oh god...
Ready, start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Come on, IRyS!
Keep going!
I can't... my feet...
Five seconds left!
Time's up!
You did it! You did great!
I tried my best...
You don't have to keep standing there! Step off!
Oh, thank god.
I'm not gonna go that hard, I'm not...
Bijou's Pebbles are gonna help me?
Yeah, she's sharing them.
All right, well, I'll try to just do my best.
Ouch... okay, I'm good.
Okay, ready, start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two!
Twenty-three! Twenty-four!
Twenty-five! Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Thirty-one! Thirty-two!
Time's up!
Whoa! Nice, Calli!
You did great!
I'm good... I'm good...
You got more than your first time!
Yeah, 32! Your form was perfect!
So, how many did she touch? It was...
And the final count is 32!
Whoa! Yay!
I'll take it.
Step on those pebbles like they're mud.
Who gives you permission?
Yeah, who gave you permission? I did!
Whoa! Ow!
She's going Super Saiyan!
Yeah! Oh, dear.
Something's coming out of me.
All right, Zeta, are you ready? Yeah!
Three, two, one, go!
One, two, three...
Four, five, six...
Seven, eight, nine, ten...
Eleven, twelve, thirteen...
Fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen...
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty-one...
Twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five...
Twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine...
Thirty, thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three...
Thirty-four, thirty-five, thirty-six...
Thirty-seven, thirty-eight, thirty-nine...
Time's up! Whoa!
Yay!
This is Zeta's potential. My butt, my butt.
Yeah! So cool!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For Level 3, I've got a little something...
...behind me, which is...
...a cup! A cup!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Um, maybe later. Oh, not tea time? Oh.
While you guys are stepping... while we are stepping on the...
...bumpy mat...
...we're also going to be balancing this cup on top of our head like this!
No! Oh my god! And we still have to use the mat?
We still have to? It's a combination of everything!
Yeah. And while lifting as well, of course.
Yeah, it doesn't affect us at all! Not at all!
It doesn't affect us! Okay, crown!
Give her the crown. Crown the princess.
There you go. It's so over.
It's so over!
All right, people, are you ready?
Remember to use your butt and your legs. Form is important.
Okay, butt and legs. Form!
Yes. All right. Are you ready?
Yeah! Okay, start!
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
Oh, it's tilted! Oh no!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen...
Seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty...
Twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three...
Oh! She fell!
But she's keeping it! She's keeping it on her head!
Go, go, go, go! Five, four, three, two, one...
Time's up! Whoa!
How many was that? I like how the cup was like stuck on her head.
Yeah, that was funny. And then it turned over and it was hot on her head.
Oh, that was so funny.
28! You got 28! Yeah!
Iris, it's IRyS! IRyS is princess!
I have to do this... Beautiful posture!
Exactly, yeah! Look at that posture!
This is her strong point because she is so good at keeping it on her head.
Don't lose your posture!
Wait a sec, don't put it on me yet. Don't put it on me yet.
Okay, you may place it on my head, my ladies.
Here it goes. Thank you. Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, my coronation...
Three, two, one, start!
One, two...
Oh, she dropped it! She dropped it!
Okay, go, go!
Four, five...
Six, seven... Yeah!
It's going toward... Oh my god.
Okay, keep going, keep going!
Oh, she dropped it again!
Eight, nine, ten...
Eleven, twelve...
I don't know how you guys did this!
Time's up! Whoa!
Aww...
I'm proud of you. This stupid cup! Stupid cup!
Don't blame the cup. It's not the cup's fault. Okay.
Maybe my good form will come in handy here.
Yeah, exactly! You may place the tiara on my head.
Okay. No, you have to step on it first.
Oh, come on! Yes, you have to step first!
It's the pain before... Yeah, pain before the gain.
Pain is beauty. All right, all right, let's do it.
I shall place it on top of her crown.
So you have double crown!
Okay, okay.
Are you ready, Calli? Maybe. Okay, maybe.
Three, two, one, start!
One, two...
Three, four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Ten...
Eleven...
Twelve...
Thirteen...
Fourteen...
Fifteen...
Sixteen...
Seventeen...
Eighteen...
Nineteen...
Twenty...
Twenty-one...
Twenty-two...
Twenty-three...
Twenty-four!
Time's up!
Is it enough to win?
That was my goal!
Yeah, 24!
And I didn't lose the teacup once.
You sure didn't!
Yeah, maybe there was tape on it?
Maybe there was tape on it.
No, no!
Super glue?
Put it on IRyS's head. Put it...
Let's really test it, let's really get in there.
You're using me as the test dummy?
It's Zeta's turn.
Yeah!
Yeah, you've got it.
Right in the center of your head so that it's less likely to fall off.
This is like the best birthday ever.
Aw, yay, I'm glad.
Now then, are you ready?
Three, two, one, start!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Ten...
Eleven...
Twelve...
Thirteen...
Fourteen...
Fifteen...
Sixteen...
Seventeen...
Eighteen...
Nineteen...
Twenty...
Twenty-one...
Oh, it fell!
Hurry up!
Okay...
Twenty-two...
Twenty-three...
Twenty-four...
Twenty-five...
Twenty-six!
Time's up!
What's what's what's?
You did it! 26 is your final number.
Yay!
Does that mean the scores are what I think they are?
I think so!
Is anyone keeping the score?
Staff-san has been keeping score for us.
Yes, Zeta is our winner!
I am!
You are!
What are the scores again?
What matters is what's inside.
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo!
Some of you were able to lift pretty well.
Maybe not for some, though.
It was so much fun just watching!
But come on, Zeta! You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills or something!
Prove it to us next test, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me! This is Amelia Watson signing off. Until next time! Bye!
Bye Ame!
Ame has really high standards, okay? Even if you won...
Not enough for her.
Thank you so much!
Congratulations!
Group hug!
Bye-bye!
See ya!
おい！ちょっと、ちょっと！
Hey! Wait, wait!
おい！
Hey!
何事、何事？
What's going on, what's going on?
あいつ狙おう！
Let's aim at her!
あ、当たっ... あ、あ、う、当たった！あ！
Ah, it hit... Ah, ah, oh, I got hit! Ah!
なかなか倒されない
She won't go down easily.
倒れた、倒れた
She fell, she fell.
ちっちゃ、ちっちゃい
So small, so small.
こいつ超えろよ、こいつ超えろよ
Go beyond this, go beyond this!
超えろ、超えろ、超えろ、超えろ、死ぬ
Go beyond, go beyond! I'm gonna die!
嫌だ、嫌だ
No, no!
弱すぎる！
Too weak!
うわ、冷たい！
Whoa, it's cold!
こっち、こっち、おい！おい、おい、おい
This way, this way, hey! Hey, hey, hey
はい、はい、はい。はい、はい
Yes, yes, yes. Yes, yes.
楽しそう、楽しそう
Looks fun, looks fun.
やめて、やめて
Stop, stop!
あ、ゼータ！
Ah, Zeta!
何？何？
What? What?
何で水鉄砲持ってるの？
Why are you holding a water gun?
え、やばい、やばい
Wait, no, no!
え、ちょっと待って
Wait, wait a minute!
やめて、やめて！
Stop, stop!
やばい、やばい
Oh no, oh no!
当たった、当たった
It hit, it hit!
お、お
Oh, oh...
持てるよ
I can hold it!
早いの、もう、それ
Is it already that fast?
持ってるよ、持ってるよ
I'm holding it, I'm holding it!
おー！
Ohhh!
どういうこと？誰か説明して〜！
What does this mean? Someone explain~!
Bokobokobo- Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehek!
Zeta, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
I already told them what to do before you came here, so they know the rules!
この水鉄砲で君のエイム力を確かめるよ！
We're gonna be testing your aim skills with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many immobile targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
In level 2, we will see how many moving targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
And level 3 will test if you can hit the targets on the moving zombie!
Who do you think is the best shooter here?
俺だ！
Me!
俺だ、俺だ、俺だ！
Me, me, me!
はい！
Yes!
とわ達、みんななんとFPSやってるんだね。
We all play FPS games, you know.
そうだね、私。
That's right.
私はやってないけどね！
I don't play them, though!
余裕よ、余裕
It's a breeze, a piece of cake.
あ、がんばろう
Ah, let's do our best.
誰が勝つんでしょうかという感じなんですか？
So, who do you think is going to win?
まあ負けませんよ
Well, I won't lose.
私も負けないよ！
I won't lose either!
Level 1
おおー！
Ooh!
動かない的があるので、こちらをみんなで1人ずつ撃っていこうかなと思います
There are stationary targets, so let's take turns shooting them one by one.
がんばる！
I'll do my best!
順番どうしましょう？
What should we do about the order?
やりたい！やりたい！やりたい！やりたい！
I want to go! I want to go! I want to go! I want to go!
まつりちゃんは撃ちやすい位置...
Matsuri-chan, stand in an easy-to-shoot position...
他の3人はここら辺で見てもらいましょう
The other three of us can watch from around here.
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
おお！上手い！
Wow! She's good!
ごめん
Sorry.
あ、ごめん
Ah, sorry.
え？
Eh?
まつりさん、パーフェクトおじさん？
Matsuri-san, are you a perfect uncle?
パーフェクト！
Perfect!
え？
Eh?
うますぎる！
She's too good!
やばい、うますぎる
This is crazy, she's too good!
残り15秒！
15 seconds remaining!
ええ？これみんなには分かんないけど、きついよ、これ
What? You guys might not get it, but this is really tough!
すごい、すごい！
Amazing, amazing!
え、これ最後？
Eh, is this the last one?
ええ？
Eh?
最後！
The last one!
すごーい！完璧！
Amazing! Perfect!
まつりちゃん、一発も外さず、全て取れました！
Matsuri-chan got all of them without missing a single shot!
すごーい！うますぎる！
Amazing! You're too good!
ちょっと行きづらいわ
It's a bit hard to follow that...
じゃあ、私行く
Then, I'll go.
あ、待って、トワ様でしょう！次！
Ah, wait, shouldn't it be Towa-sama next?
トワ様？じゃあ、トワ
Towa-sama? Okay, Towa.
がんばれ！
Do your best!
支える、支える感じで！
Support me, stand by me!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
ここ！
Here!
そこ！
There!
おお、早い！早い！
Oh, so fast! So fast!
早い！
Fast!
ここ！
Here!
早い！
Fast!
ここ！
Here!
ちょっと待って、うまい！
Wait a sec, she's good!
うまい、うまい、めっちゃ早い！
She's good, she's good, so fast!
ここ！
Here!
早い！
Fast!
すごーい！クリアー！
Amazing! Clear!
だんだん超えてくんだ、これ
The scores keep getting higher.
次はどうする？
Who's next?
いや、先にやってよ！先にやって！
No, you go first! You go first!
とりあえずね
Anyway...
下半身作戦、下半身作戦
Lower body strategy, lower body strategy.
下半身を安定させる、ブレないように
Stabilizing the lower body so there's no shaking.
下半身つけてきたと
Focusing on the lower body.
ポーズだっせえ！ダサすぎる！これでいくから
That pose is so lame! Too lame! But I'm going with this.
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, Go!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
あ、当たってる、当たってる
Ah, she's hitting them, she's hitting them!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
いや、適当に撃って...
No, just shooting randomly...
あ、でも惜しい、惜しい！
Ah, but close, so close!
惜しい、惜しい！どうなってる？
Close, so close! What's happening?
もうちょい上！もうちょい上！
A bit higher! A bit higher!
がんばれ、がんばれ！
Do your best, do your best!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
ラプラスの結果は、まぁ、ひどい結果に
Laplus' result was, well, a terrible result...
最後、いきますか
Shall we do the last one?
いきます！がんばれー！
Let's go! Do your best!
ということで、最後ゼタ、じゃあ撃ちます
And so, finally, Zeta will shoot.
1秒で、1秒で！いやいやいや
In 1 second, in 1 second! No, no, no!
準備オッケー？準備オッケー
Are you ready? Ready!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
うわー！当たった、当たった！
Wow! She hit it, she hit it!
うまい！
Nice!
すごい、うまい！
Amazing, nice!
思ったより上手い！上手い！
Better than expected! Nice!
いや、これは...
No, this is...
うわー！
Wow!
全然余裕、余裕
Piece of cake, piece of cake.
え、あと一個、あと一個
Eh, one more, one more.
どこだ？どこだ？
Where is it? Where is it?
右、右！下、下、下！
Right, right! Down, down, down!
下、下！
Down, down!
どこにある？どこ？タイムアップ！
Where is it? Where? Time's up!
あれ？壊れた！
Huh? It broke!
え、何これ？
Eh, what is this?
神様が手伝ってくれた？
Did God help her?
まつり先輩ナイスショット！
Matsuri-senpai, nice shot!
滑り込みでハーフクリア！
Slipped in for a half clear!
すごーい！クリアー！
Amazing! Clear!
Level 2
あちらをご覧ください！
Please look over there!
動いてる！めちゃくちゃ動いてる！
They're moving! They're moving like crazy!
はい、がんばっていきましょう！
Yes, let's do our best!
じゃあ、誰からいく？
Then, who goes first?
俺だ！俺だ！俺だ！
Me! Me! Me!
私もいきたい！
I want to go too!
もういっちゃったから、ラプラスで
She already went, so let's go with Laplus.
やったもん勝ちでやばい
First come first served, this is wild.
ではいきましょう、ラプラス！
Let's go, Laplus!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
このゲームには必勝法がある
There is a surefire way to win this game.
めっちゃ回っとるやん！
She's spinning so much!
回るな！
Don't spin!
後ろから撃つのやばいって
Shooting from behind is crazy!
当たってないよ！当たってない！
It's not hitting! It's not hitting!
当たってないよ！
It's not hitting!
当たってない！
腕、腕、腕...
Your arms, arms, arms...
ぐるんぐるんだから、カメラ
Because the camera is spinning round and round.
しゃっ！ / おおー
Hup! / Ooh-
え、あと5秒しかないよ！
Wait, there are only 5 seconds left!
1個しか倒してない！
You've only downed one!
1個しか倒してないよ！
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Good luck! Good luck!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
でもすごいよ、1個！
But one is amazing!
もう1個撃とう、もう1個撃とう。
Let's shoot one more, let's shoot one more.
あの、後ろ向きでね...
Well, since I was facing backwards...
ゼータ行きたい！
Zeta wants to go!
ゼータ行きたい？
Zeta wants to go?
うん、行きたい、行きたい！
Yeah, I want to, I want to!
はい、じゃあ、ゼータ行きました！
Alright, next up is Zeta!
頑張て、ゼータ君！
Do your best, Zeta-kun!
ラプラスみたいに後ろ向かなくていい？
Do you not need to face backward like Laplus?
うん、大丈夫！
Yeah, I'm fine!
メートル調整行きましょう！
Let's go for the range adjustment!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
スタート！
Start!
頑張れ！
Good luck!
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、当たってない！当たってない！
Wait, wait, wait, it's not hitting! It's not hitting!
むずい、むずい。
It's hard, it's hard.
むずい！
It's hard!
いや、回ってるんだけど、頭が。
Wait, my head is spinning.
回ってる、回ってる。
Spinning, spinning.
あ、当たった、当たった、当たった！
Ah, it hit, it hit, it hit!
裏面だったな。
It was on the back side.
あ、裏面はダメ。
Ah, the back side doesn't count.
やばい、ゼータ後ろ！
Oh no, Zeta, behind you!
これはもう後ろ！
This is from behind!
うわっ！
Uwah!
頑張れ、いけるから！
Good luck, you can do it!
おっ、ああっ！
Oh, ah!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
ということで、残念。ゼータ、1枚です！
And so, unfortunately, Zeta got 1 target!
むっちゃ難しそう、これ。
This looks so difficult.
これむずいよ。
This is hard.
いや、でも惜しかったね。
But that was close.
裏がやばい、裏が。
The back side is crazy, the back.
裏面だったからすごい惜しい。
It was on the back, so it was really close.
最後嫌だから、もう次に行かせてください。
I don't want to go last, so please let me go next.
回ろう、回ろう。
Let's spin, let's spin.
行っちゃった、行っちゃった。もう行っちゃった。
She went, she went. She already went.
まつり先輩、行くぞ！
Matsuri-senpai, here I go!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
スタート！
Start!
待って、おお、惜しい！
Wait, oh, close!
おお、惜しい！
Oh, close!
え、今のダメ？
Eh, that didn't count?
ダメなん... お、おっ！
It didn't... oh, oh!
おおー！すごい！
Ooh! Amazing!
2個目！
Second one!
え、今んとこ最高記録だよ、これ。
Eh, she has the highest score so far.
そうだよね、2個の時点でね。
Right, already at 2.
むずいんだから、これ。
Because this is hard.
むずい、うわっ、うわっ！
It's hard, uwah, uwah!
狙ってるうちに、どんどん時間が過ぎてって...
While I'm aiming, the time is just ticking away...
これ後ろじゃない？後ろじゃない？
Isn't this the back? Isn't this the back?
後ろはね、もうあの...
The back side is, well...
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
弱い。
I'm weak.
弱いのではありません。
You are not weak.
くっそー、2個か。
Damn, only 2?
いや、2個でも1位だよ、1位。
But even with 2, you're in 1st place.
なんかこれ、気づいたぞ、あち。
Somehow, I realized something.
追わない方がいいよ。
It's better not to chase them.
絶対そう！トワも思ってた。
Absolutely! Towa thought so too.
一点集中で、来たところをパーンの方が。
Focus on one spot and shoot when they come.
いいね。
Sounds good.
アドバイスを活かして、やろうかな。
I'll try using that advice.
トワちん挑戦！
Towachin's challenge!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
スタート！
Start!
頑張れ！
Good luck!
おらっ！はいっ！
Ora! Yes!
おお、惜しい！惜しい！
Oh, close! Close!
やばい、こっち向け！
Oh no, turn this way!
やばい！
Oh no!
裏だ！裏、うわっ、うわっ！
It's the back! The back, uwah, uwah!
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Good luck, good luck!
おお、行けた、行けた！
Oh, she got it, she got it!
あと10秒。
10 seconds left.
頑張れ！
Good luck!
タイミングだ、タイミングだ。
It's about timing, timing.
全部裏。これまずい！
All on the back. This is bad!
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
これ難しいんだよ！
This is so hard!
え、これ、くそむずいじゃん。
Eh, this is super hard.
1枚でした。
It was 1 target.
一緒だ、トワさん。
We got the same, Towa-san.
申し訳ないけど、後ろの人と一緒。
Sorry to say, but I'm the same as the person in the back.
Level 3
普通の的、動く的と来て、なんとこちら！ぽん！
First standard targets, then moving targets, and now we have this! Bam!
ゾンビ！きもい！
Zombie! Gross!
動いてる！
It's moving!
ゾンビの、あの、動く的になってます。
The zombie has become the moving target.
でも的自体は2つしかない。
But there are only two targets.
確かに。
True.
こちらを狙って...なんか気持ち悪いポーズもしてます。
Aiming for these... it's also making some gross poses.
こいつ自我があるぞ、自我が。
This guy has a mind of its own!
トワちんから、じゃあ行きましょう！
Let's start with Towachin then!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
スタート！
Start!
え、動く、え、ごめん。
Eh, it's moving... wait, sorry.
え、イージー、イージー、イージー。
Eh, easy, easy, easy.
え、でもなんか...おい、おい、こっち向け！こっち向け！
Eh, but somehow... hey, hey, look this way! Look this way!
やばい。
Oh no.
いや、ちょっと待って。
No, wait a minute.
待って、やばい、やばい。
Wait, oh no, oh no.
あと1枚！頭の！
One more left! On the head!
止まるんだ。
Stop moving.
やばい、おい！
Oh no, hey!
なんか...
Somehow...
頑張れ！
Good luck!
よっしゃ、おー！クリア！
Yes, oh! Clear!
ギリギリでした！
That was close!
2つ、ちゃんと割れました。ありがとうございます。
Both targets were successfully broken. Thank you very much.
なんか、ゾンビがたまに自我を持ち始めて、不思議な動きをするので、みなさん注意を。
The zombie sometimes seems to develop a mind of its own and make strange moves, so everyone, watch out.
行きたい、行きたい！
I want to go, I want to go!
じゃあ、ねーねちゃんね。 / 頑張るぞー！
Alright, big sis then. / I'll do my best!
じゃあ、まつりちゃん。
Alright, Matsuri-chan.
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, go!
スタート！はやっ、はやっ、おー、はやっ！
Start! Fast! Fast! Oh, fast!
ええっ？！はやっ！
Ehh?! So fast!
あの、3秒で終わりました。
Um, she finished in 3 seconds.
3秒！
3 seconds!
あ、３、２、１、GO！
Ah, 3, 2, 1, go!
お、のけぞってる！のけぞってる！
Oh! It's backing away! It's backing away!
これ、まずい？これ、まずい？
Wait, is this bad?
やっちゃった、やっちゃった！
I did it! I actually did it!
今、まつりちゃんが３秒で撃ち抜いちゃったということは…
Since Matsuri-chan shot it down in three seconds...
たぶんもう次のゾンビは、この動きしちゃいけないなっていう風になって…
...the next zombie will probably learn not to make those movements.
やばい！学習するタイプだ！
Oh no! It's the type that learns!
学習しちゃいます、学習ゾンビなんだ
It's learning! It's an adaptive zombie!
ちょっと待って、じゃあ、先にやる？先にやる？
Wait! Then who's going next? Who's next?
じゃあ、ラプ様が先にやる？先にやる？
Then, will La+-sama go next?
主役が最後でしょ！
The star of the show should go last!
３、２、１、スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
あははは、やばい！
Ahahaha, oh no!
当たるんかい！なんで当たるんだよ！
I got hit?! Why did I get hit?!
やばい！おもしろすぎる！
This is bad! This is too funny!
やばい、やばい！うわああ！
Oh no, oh no! Nooo!
撃って、撃って！撃って撃って撃って！
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot, shoot, shoot!
いいよ、いいよ！ラプ様、落ち着いて！
You can do it! Calm down, La+-sama!
あ、当たる、当たる！
Ah, it's going to hit!
やばい、やばい、よけてよけて！
Oh no! Dodge, dodge!
うわ！え、何それ？！
Whoa! What was that?!
そういうゲーム？！あははは！
Is this that kind of game?! Ahahaha!
やばい、ちょっと途中で我慢できなかった
Oh no, I couldn't hold back my laughter.
難しすぎて！
It was too hard!
最後の挑戦はゼタ！３、２、１、GO！
The final challenger is Zeta! 3, 2, 1, go!
うわああ！めっちゃ動いてる、めっちゃ動いてる！
Whoa! It's moving so much! It's moving like crazy!
当たってる当たってる！めっちゃ動いてるよ！
She's hitting it! But it's moving so much!
よけて、よけて！私も守って！
Dodge, dodge! Protect me too!
やばい、やばい、これ！
Oh no, this is crazy!
お、翻弄されてる！お、あと1枚！
Oh, she's playing with it! Just one more!
当たらない、かっこいい！
She didn't get hit! So cool!
すごかった！本当に！
That was amazing! Seriously!
すごかった！めっちゃ軽やかだった！
That was incredible! You were so light on your feet!
ということは、２倍のゼタさん！
Which means, Double Zeta-san!
Guys! Should we see who got the most points in this test?!
おお！めっちゃいい勝負！
Whoa! That's a super close match!
まつりが12点、はい！
Matsuri got 12 points, yes!
で、トワちんが11点、はい！
And Towa-chin got 11 points, yes!
で、ゼタが10点
Zeta got 10 points...
そして、ラプラスが…14点！
And La+ is... 14 points?!
４点！４点！
4 points! 4 points!
ラプラスが最下位！
La+ is in last place!
１位、１位の方へ！１位の方祝ってよ！
Look at first place! Congratulate the first place!
Woooow! Congrats!
You guys did very well!
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun!
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve
your aiming skills in the future, like me.
Oi...
Um, I'm... I'm talking here.
Oi! Listen to Kobo!
Anyway, Zeta!
You still have a long, long way to go to become a full-fledged secret agent, okay?
Yeah, let's have a match one day!
Bye! See ya~
またね、またね！バイバイ！
See ya, see ya! Bye bye!
またバトルしようよ！
Let's battle again!
またねー！
See ya!
はぁ、はぁ、うわあ！
Ah... Wow!
That was so crazy! I got wet!
from the water gun. We were shooting each other like crazy.
I even... I even had to change my clothes!
Ah... But, I heard there's going to be announcements today.
So, are you guys ready for the announcements? A little ad break, yes?
では、告知です！お願いします！
So, here's the announcement! Please!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
うわあ、眩しい！
Whoa, so bright!
She's shining... she's shining so bright! Oh my god!
Zeta in an angelic outfit...
Isn't that so cute? Angel costume.
You guys have always said that you're scared of me, so...
you can't be scared of me now, cause...
I'm... I mean, I'm kind of... I'm the most seiso person there is, so...
清楚ゼタ、清楚ゼタ来た！
Seiso Zeta, seiso Zeta is here!
どう？可愛い？可愛いでしょ？
How is it? Is it cute? It's cute, right?
真っ白だし！The costume looks so cute, right?
It's pure white! The costume looks so cute, right?
Lucu banget kan, guys? Karena kalian lagi bisa lihat seiso Zeta ya, guys ya.
It's so cute, right guys? Since you can see seiso Zeta again, guys.
Ber-costume, ber-cosplay sebagai angel-angel gitu, lucu. Iya, iya, Zeta lucu, lucu, aku mau! Siapa yang mau? Aku, aku!
Costumed, cosplaying as an angel like that, so cute. Yes, Zeta is cute, I want it! Who wants it? Me, me!
But, we don't stop here, because...
obviously, there's going to be so many more items, and we're going to introduce them now.
じゃ、こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
So, please look at this! Here we go!
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
And that are how many, but that's probably six, right? Isn't that so awesome?!
And that's how many, but that's probably six, right? Isn't that so awesome?!
That's so cool!
So, we have acrylic diorama...
So, we have an acrylic diorama...
...which you can put on your table, later we'll explain.
...which you can put on your table, which we'll explain later.
And we have a cap, no cap, okay.
We have a plushie, nuigurumi!
We have a plushie, a plushie!
And not only that, there will of course be voice...
...sorry, why did I say "voice"? There will be voice pack.
...sorry, why did I say "voice"? There will be a voice pack.
And also, bonus card as well.
And also, a bonus card as well.
Who wants bonus cards? Me!
So, I bet you guys are interested in this, yeah, definitely.
Kalau kalian tertarik, bakal ada 6 item ya guys, acrylic diorama, haori...
If you're interested, there will be 6 items guys: acrylic diorama, haori...
...kucing, eh kucing? Ada...
...cat, eh cat? There's...
...topi, ada juga boneka.
...a cap, and also a plushie.
Mmm, ippai arimasu yo ne. Mmm, bonus card, there's also bonus cards, so...
Mm, there are a lot, right? Mm, bonus card, there's also bonus cards, so...
...yeah. Definitely, we're gonna get into it. But stay...
...stay there, we're not, we're not done yet. We're not done yet.
Hai, tsugi douzo!
Alright, next please!
Jajang! This is my acrylic diorama.
Ta-da! This is my acrylic diorama.
So cute! Arutera-mama-sensei...
...thank you so much, sensei!
Mama, arigatou!
Mama, thank you!
Mama's drawing is always so cute. Kawaii desho ne. Kawaii.
Mama's drawing is always so cute. It's cute, right? Cute.
Zeta tonderu yo.
Zeta is flying.
Sugoku nai?
Isn't that amazing?
It's super-duper cute!
I'm having an al- I was, I was gonna say allergic reaction.
I am having, uh, do you know that cute aggression? Yeah.
That's what I'm feeling, it's so cute!
Okay!
Of course, we're gonna, uh, go to the next one. We have so much more.
Ja, tsugi douzo!
Then, next please!
Jajang!
Ta-da!
Nandatto?! Haori?!
What's that?! A haori?!
This is Zeta, the Vestia Zeta Haori!
I know that you guys would love to wear this at like, events, or like, concerts...
...or maybe, you know, for, for future Fest?
Next Fest. I mean...
...you guys can wear it together! You can like, huddle up wearing the same haori.
And it would be so cute, right?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform, so you guys can be, this can be your uniform.
Mmm, mmm, live no toki toka, mmm.
Mm, mm, like during live concerts, mm.
Kawaii desho. Like, mmm.
It's cute, right? Like, mm.
If everyone like, uses it together, it's gonna be so cute. Lucu banget guys, haori.
If everyone like, uses it together, it's gonna be so cute. It's really cute guys, the haori.
Aku nggak tahu mau ngomong apa, pokoknya ini keren banget. Karena desainnya itu pertama simple.
I don't know what to say, basically this is really cool. Because the design is first of all simple.
Terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
Then on the back, you can see Zeta.
Terus, nggak norak gitu lho guys. Kayak keren aja, kayak simple, keren, cool.
And it's not tacky at all, guys. It's just cool, like simple, cool, cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakainya bisa ke mana aja, nggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
So you can also wear it anywhere, it doesn't have to be just for concerts.
You can like, wear this, like, outside of concerts as well because like, it's like a sophisticated...
...ele- I wouldn't say elegant. It's like a cool-looking, like, toned-down haori, you know?
So, befitting for me, the cool secret agent. Okay, anyways...
...there's more. There's more.
Tsugi no, jajang!
The next one, ta-da!
Jajang! Wow! Uwee...
Ta-da! Wow! Uwee...
...uwee cap! I almost choked on myself.
It's so good! It's a baseball cap.
It's so cool. You can use this to shield yourself from the sun, like I do.
Because I hate the sun. There's like "uwee" written on top of the cap.
Kawaii! "Uwee" kaiteru yo. So, so, so.
Cute! It has "uwee" written on it. Yes, yes, yes.
Zeta no serifu, "uwee" tte kaiteru. Kawaii desho?
Zeta's catchphrase, it says "uwee". It's cute, right?
Of course there's like, my neko... ah, not neko, my, uh, my hair buns.
Kuping, kuping Zeta? There's my hair buns there.
Ears, Zeta's ears? There's my hair buns there.
And my, uh, ribbon. I would call this ribbon. Ignore the whiskers, but...
...if you can ignore the whiskers, those are not cat whiskers. But it's cute! You can wear it.
Cap! Buy this cap! It's a good cap.
No cap! It's so cute!
Topi ya guys. Apalagi panas-panas, harus pakai topi nggak sih guys, panas-panas.
A cap, guys. Especially when it's hot, you've got to wear a cap, right guys, when it's hot.
Apalagi silau gitu, keren kalau pakai topi lho guys.
Especially when it's glaring, you look cool if you wear a cap, guys.
Mmm. Terus keren lagi hitam gitu topinya, keren, keren, keren.
Mm. Plus, it's cool that the cap is black like that, cool, cool, cool.
Mmm. Mada aru no kana? Mmm.
Mm. Is there more? Mm.
Mmm. Aru to omou, mmm. Ja, tsugi douzo!
Mm. I think there is, mm. Then, next please!
Ugh! Ah! I... Ugh...
It's like... it's so cute!
It's, uh, with the cat headband, it's...
It's, it's called the Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie.
It looks like a cat, I know, but I swear it's not, okay?
It's not. It's, um...
If you noticed, it's based on my Cat Day KV.
So it's so cute, right?
みんな あの
Everyone, um...
Cat Dayのとき覚えてる？
Do you remember Cat Day?
これ, This is the goods from, last time.
This is the merchandise from last time.
It's so cute, right?
Look at those eyes!
It's so cute! I want to squish it and...
...jumble it up.
It's so cute!
And he's like sleeping because, um...
I heard that cats nap for 16 hours.
Although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying.
Um, it's so cute! It's like sleeping.
眠そう。眠そうなゼータちゃん。
Looks sleepy. Sleepy Zeta-chan.
眠いゼータちゃん。可愛い！
Sleepy Zeta-chan. So cute!
Buy it or else! Or else...
You don't want to miss this because...
...everyone liked the Cat Day KV, you won't miss this.
Okay! Even more, let's see.
Next, please! 次、お願いします！
Next, please! Next, please!
ボイス！うわー、ボイス！
Voice! Wow, voice!
ボイス...
Voice...
And it's titled "A Fateful Meeting".
Last but not least, there's also a bonus...
...for who purchases the full set!
Okay, full setを買ってくれた人が...
Okay, people who buy the full set...
...ボーナスをもらえるよ！
...will get a bonus!
Okay, okay. Kalian dapat bonus kalau kalian beli full set, okay?
Okay, okay. You'll get a bonus if you buy the full set, okay?
So...
Last one, please!
最後お願いします！
The last one, please!
じゃじゃーん！Here's the bonus! Oh!
Ta-da! Here's the bonus! Oh!
It's the limited edition!
You'll get my signature, okay?
It's so good!
It's like hand-written signature and all that.
It's like a hand-written signature and all that.
It's the best! It's limited, so get it now!
Limited... スペシャルだよね、一番。
Limited... It's special, the best one.
スペシャル。
Special.
Of course, um...
It's a little ad break, but we are not gonna stop there.
Because, even though it's my birthday,
I want to gift to you instead, yeah!
But it's not over yet!
これで終わりじゃないよ！
This isn't the end!
It's my birthday, but I also want to give you a present as well, so...
Aren't you excited?
Okay, let's go get your present!
goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone.
止めらんない熱 身任せて
Leaving myself to this unstoppable heat.
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm sick of the rules, break it down.
我慢出来ない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free.
目があらんでしまいそうな
So dazzling that it almost blinds me,
出立ちのマーメイド 憧れてたっけ
the mermaid's style—did I once admire it?
But then 今は何も響かない
But then, now nothing resonates with me.
I know who I am, ay
「ブランディング」にはあっかんべー
Sticking my tongue out at "branding",
今は完全無視よ 何でもありの Greedy style
totally ignoring it now, anything goes in my greedy style.
ダサいやっかみも興味ないの
I have no interest in lame jealousy,
ありのままでいたい
I just want to be myself.
goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone.
止めらんない熱 身任せて
Leaving myself to this unstoppable heat.
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm sick of the rules, break it down.
我慢出来ない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free.
We are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
揺るがない Pride それだけでいいの
An unwavering pride, that's all I need.
たらればだらけの Lowな日々を Break it down, break it
These low days full of "what-ifs", break it down, break it.
We are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
No matter what anyone says, I will sing.
アンフェアばかりの セカイなど Break it down, break it ススメ
An unfair world and such, break it down, break it, move forward.
Break it down, break it ススメ
Break it down, break it, move forward.
I just don't care about you!
ハイテクなメイクやファッション
High-tech makeup and fashion,
Self-love には敵わないよ
can't compete with self-love.
この身と心 誰の物でも無いでしょ
This body and heart belong to no one else, right?
いい加減いい大人だよね...？
Aren't we grown-up enough already...? Trump card?
Inilah aku apa adanya, tidak sempurna, tapi sepenuhnya diriku
This is who I am, not perfect, but fully myself.
でも今は楽しいよ ありのままでいられるから！
But right now I'm having fun, because I can be myself!
goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone.
止めらんない熱 身任せて
Leaving myself to this unstoppable heat.
こりごりだ Rule は Break it down
I'm sick of the rules, break it down.
我慢出来ない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free.
We are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
揺るがない Pride それだけでいいの
An unwavering pride, that's all I need.
たらればだらけの Lowな日々を Break it down, break it
These low days full of "what-ifs", break it down, break it.
We are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
No matter what anyone says, I will sing.
アンフェアばかりのセカイなど
A world full of nothing but unfairness...
break it down, break it ススメ
Break it down, break it, move forward!
can't break me down, breaking me
break it down, break it down
Let's go! break it down, break it ススメ
Let's go! Break it down, break it, move forward!
break it down, break it down
goin' goin' my way
もうほっといて
Just leave me alone.
止めらんない熱 任せて
Leave it to this unstoppable passion.
こりごりだ Rule は break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down!
我慢出来ない let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free!
Thank you everyone!
Now let's break it down!
Secretary, if you like it, make some noise!
MISSION COMPLETE!
[On-screen] MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, ZECRETARY!
[On-screen] MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, ZECRETARY!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! :D
[On-screen] YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! :D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...!
[On-screen] LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...!
KEEP BREAKING IT DOWN!
[On-screen] KEEP BREAKING IT DOWN!